{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"7704/0.13",
			"answer":"7704/0.13",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.806/0.13",
			"answer":"2.806/0.13",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3900/0.095",
			"answer":"3900/0.095",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"71.44/1.6",
			"answer":"71.44/1.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.065/0.65",
			"answer":"8.065/0.65",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2103/60",
			"answer":"2103/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1889/54",
			"answer":"1889/54",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9967/61",
			"answer":"9967/61",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2336/18",
			"answer":"2336/18",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4519/91",
			"answer":"4519/91",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}